# Tran Ngoc Hung

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam



trhung26620@gmail.com +84789978995





Portfolio: trhung26620.github.io



linkedin.com/in/hung-tran-0829a1209

## Summary

I graduated with a bachelor's degree in Information Assurance in 2022. However, I started working for a company providing cyber security services in 2021 with the job of Web/App Penetrating Testing. During nearly 2 years, my main job is as a security researcher, programming vulnerability testing tools, finding and exploiting vulnerabilities for Websites/Applications related to the fields: bank, finance, insurance, hospital,...

Recently, when I had the opportunity to learn about blockchain, I was extremely interested in the strengths of this technology, so I decided to learn and develop Web3 projects. Regarding my future plans, I want to be an expert in the blockchain field in the next 3 years.

## **Experience**



### Blockchain Researcher

Sep 2022 - Current

Self-study on Web3, Blockchain, Dapps and develop personal projects such as: NFT Marketplace, Booking Care Dapp, Charity DAO App



#### **Web/App Pentester**

Techlab Corporation

May 2021 - Feb 2023 (21 months)

- Develop tools for penetration testing
- Find and exploit security vulnerabilities of websites, Android/IOS applications -Build security checklist (Database and programming language) for developers

#### **Education**



#### FPT University (Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam)

Undergraduate, Information Assurance 2018 - 2022

#### **Skills**

```
HTML • CSS • JavaScript • Web Development • Cyber Security • NodeJS • Solidity •
Crypto • ReactJS • Python • Express • Database
```